



Md. Ridoy Khan

Senior Front End Developer

Assalamualaikum, I'm Md. Ridoy Khan! I am a Senior Front-End Developer at Pixency, specializing in HTML, WordPress (Elementor), React.js, and Next.js. With 3+ years of professional experience and 6 months of internship at Pixency, I have been dedicated to building user-friendly and responsive websites since January 3, 2021. I hold a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering from Primeasia University and have a deep passion for programming and web development. Since 2022, I've been an approved author on ThemeForest, where I design and sell HTML5 templates. My templates are crafted to be highly functional, visually appealing, and tailored to diverse client requirements.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01 January 2022 - Present (Full Time)

Pixency, Dhaka Bangladesh

Senior Front End Developer

01 July 2021 - 01 Jan 2022 (Full Time)

Pixency, Dhaka Bangladesh

Front End Developer (Internship)

MY SKILLS

My Skills:

HTML5 || Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) || SASS || LESS || Bootstrap || JavaScript || jQuery || JavaScript eXtension (JSX) || React.js || Next.js || Wordpress Costomization || Wordpress Elementor (CMS) || Git || GitHub || Adobe Photoshop || Adobe Illustrator || Adobe XD || Figma (Software) || ClickUp || Jira || Notion || Sr. Frontend Developer.

CONTACT

69

+8801314623970 || +8801974623970



ridoykhan.cse.web@gmail.com



https://github.com/mdridoykhan138



mdridoykhan138



Banasree, Dhaka Bnagladesh

EDUCATION

BSC IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

2016 - 2020

Primeasia University, Dhaka.

HSC IN SCIENCE

2015

Dr. khandaker mosharraf hossain college, Cumilla.

PROJECTS

Speak - Education Html5 Template

Published - 14 January 2022 - (Themeforest approved)

ThemeforestLink

LiveLink

Allen - Multipurpose Saas Html5 Template

Published - 13 December 2022 - (Themeforest approved)

ThemeforestLink

LiveLink

Attor – Attorney HTML5 Template

Published - 07 Apri 2022 - **(Frontend Development)**<u>LiveLink</u>

E-Study Dashboard

Published - 01 February 2023 - **(Frontend Development) LiveLink**

Ridoy Portfolio NextJs - v15

Published - 01 December 2024 - **(Frontend Development) LiveLink**

Moon Miners HTML Template

Published - 01 March 2021 - **(Frontend Development)**<u>LiveLink</u>

Talktier Conversation HTML Template

Published - 06 September 2021 - **(Frontend Development)**<u>LiveLink</u>

Reazul Portfolio HTML5 Template

Published - 11 November 2023 - **(Frontend Development) LiveLink**

More => RaidarDashboard - RidoykEcommNextJS

And More => My NextJs - Portfolio LinkHere

HOBBIES

Socializing with friends and family, watching documentaries and news, playing football and cricket weekly, reading non-fiction, solving puzzles, fishing, and designing software and websites.